[ Mice squeaking ]
Come on , sweetie pie .
Morning , Elvis . You 're a pretty Elvis , aren 't you ?
Yes , you are .
Jesus Christ , Ronnie , you know I have to fucking work tonight .
Somebody around here has got to make some money .
I 'm all broken up here , bitch . I can 't work .
- Yeah , and whose fault is that ? - Fuck you .
Oh , my God , you 're pathetic .
You know that new waitress over at the Bingo Lounge ?
She 's been giving me the freaky eye .
Oh , the whore with the big tits hanging down to her knees ?
Maybe I 'll choke the chicken ,
purge my snorkel all over them flappy-ass tits .
Good . Well , have a good fucking time .
- I will . - I hope she likes cripples .
Bitch , I will crawl over there , and I will skull fuck the shit outta you !
Oh , I 'll get the crutches for you .
See what you did ? Fucking loudmouth .
Waah ! Waah !
That 's all that fucker does is cry .
Cry and shit . Cry and shit .
Just like you . That 's all you do is cry and shit .
Fuck you and set it on my pole right now , bitch .
Fuck off .
Mom ?
Can 't you see I 'm making eggs over here ?
I 'll pass .
Since when ?
Since now . They 're chicken abortions , and they 're fucking gross .
They are not chicken abortions .
Like you know what an abortion is .
You know what , can you please go upstairs and get your brother ?
Why do I always have to do it ?
Just do it !
Don 't you give me that look !
Man , that bitch got herself a nice little dumper .
- What did you just say ? - You heard me .
No , say it again , Ronnie ! Say it to my face !
Oh , what 's the matter ? You jealous of your own daughter 's ass ?
- Fucking pig . - Aah !
You fucking whore !
[ Baby crying ]
All right , now clean it up !
- Go on . - I 'm not gonna do this anymore !
Michael .
Stop jerking off in there .
Get away !
Hey ! Get your ass downstairs
and wash your hands , you little shit .
I 'm not listening ! Aaaahhh !
Let me tell you something .
That freak of yours , he needs some serious discipline .
I mean , he runs around like a little bitch .
You leave him alone . Keep your hands off him .
Give me a fucking break . He 's probably a queer .
He 's gonna grow up , end up cutting his dick and balls off
and changing his name to Michelle .
There he is . Good morning , Michelle , ma belle .
What the hell took you two so long ?
Elvis died . I had to flush him .
Oh , honey , I 'm sorry .
We 'll get you a new one after school , okay ?
Okay .
What 'd you do to him , stroke him to death ?
Uh , Elvis .
Elvis ! Uh ! Uh ! Uh !
You know what ? It 's a fucking rat .
Who pays money for a fucking rat ?
I mean , it 's a goddamn rat , man .
Morning , Boo .
" Morning , Boo . "
Take that damn thing off .
You are starting to annoy me , boy .
I hate you .
And I hate you , too . You see this ?
As soon as this heals , I 'm gonna break it again on your fucking face !
[ Mom ] Enough , all right ? Can we just eat in peace for once ?
[ School bell rings ]
[ Urinating ]
What a fucking pussy , dude . I told you he wouldn 't fight .
He 's all fucking talk . I was like- - We were fighting , right ?
You were there . He was like , " I 'm not gonna fight you . " I was like- -
Yes !
I know where he lives .
- You want to egg his house ? - We can totally do that .
- Yeah . - Oh .
Hey , shit-pants .
What 's going on ? You know , um ...
I heard your sister got caught selling blow jobs in the bathroom .
I heard they had to pump the cum out of her stomach .
[ Sucking sound ]
Hey , Mikey , how 's your mom doing ?
You know , my old man said that for a buck she 'd rub her tits on his face .
Shut up .
What the fuck did you say , faggot ?
- Mikey 's upset . - Look how tough he is .
Hey , ball-licker , check this out .
I was thinking of making copies of Mommy for the whole school .
- Fuck you . - Hey ! Tough guy !
Think she 'd suck my dick for a quarter and let me suck her tits ?
- Shut up ! Shut up ! - Don 't fucking yell in my face , you bitch !
Fuck off !
What the hell is going on here ?
Break it up !
I said break it up !
You over there , you over there , you there .
- He started it . - Shut up !
Fuck you .
What did you say , son ?
I said fuck you .
Fuck me ?
Come here . Come here .
- My bag ! - Grab it !
Again ? Again ? Jesus , what is it with you and this goddamn school ?
I cannot keep coming down here like this .
Look , Miss Myers ,
I do not enjoy calling you down here every five minutes .
Really ? It sure seems like you fucking do .
Can 't you get control over your school , principal ?
Yes , I can get control . I can control my school .
There 's something you gotta know .
Will you just relax a moment ? Please sit down and let me talk to you .
- Please . Please . - Okay . What ?
Please , sit down .
- Thank God . - Hi , Jim . How are you ?
Is this her ?
Miss Myers , this is Dr. Loomis . I took the liberty of calling him in .
- Happens to be a child psychologist- - - Thank you , Jim .
Psychologist ?
May I ask you ,
has your son ever had any kind of serious psychiatric evaluation ?
Okay , I 've had enough . This is crazy .
- Miss Myers , please . - I gotta get back to work .
- I gotta go . - Please , ma 'am .
We only want the best for the child . Please don 't take offense .
Please , sit down . Sit down .
Thank you .
Look , uh , Miss Myers ...
we found this ...
in Michael 's school bag .
Come on . Big deal . He found a dead cat .
And these .
What is that ?
I hope you 're not squeamish , Mrs. Myers .
Oh , God .
Oh , this is really sick .
Are you saying Michael did this ?
Michael loves animals . He- -
Why would he do this ?
Mrs. Myers , typically the thrill of hurting or causing pain to smaller creatures ,
it 's often an early warning sign .
Early warning sign for what ?
For much deeper and bigger problems .
[ Mrs. Myers ] What do you mean problems ? What is this ?
[ Loomis ] He 's a very disturbed young man .
I have to evaluate him , and I 'd like to interview him .
I need to take him through a series of tests .
[ Mrs. Myers ] Well , you can talk to him , but what does- -
what does evaluating him- - what does that mean ?
[ Loomis ] Obviously , he 's a very deranged young mind that can do this to his pets .
[ Mrs. Myers ] You don 't know that he did that .
Fuck , man , if I get one more fucking detention , I 'll be fucking expelled .
My old man 's gonna beat my ass .
We gotta get that piece of shit on the weekend so we don 't get in trouble .
Dude , if I see that Myers pussy , he 's fucking dead .
You want it ?
Huh ? Do you want it ?
Aah !
Ow !
What the fuck ?
Oh , you 're so fucking dead .
Oh , please stop .
Stop !
Please .
Please . Please no !
I 'm sorry .
Don 't hurt me . Just- - I 'm sorry .
No , no , no , don 't . Don 't . Please . Please .
Please .
Don 't hurt me .
No .
[ Thud ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Gasping ]
- [ Screaming ] - [ Thud ]
[ Music playing on TV ]
Hey , clown .
Hey .
Psycho boy .
Cat killer .
Do you really torture and kill all them worthless animals , boy ?
Make you feel like a real bad-ass motherfucker killer , huh ?
That is some deep-ass ,
serious , faggoty-ass shit , man .
Judith , I 'm gonna be late !
" Judith , I 'm gonna be late ! "
You really are a whiny little bitch , you know that ?
Ronnie , knock it off .
Ma , Judith is wasting all my time .
I really shouldn 't even let you go after that shit you pulled today at school .
Oh , Ma , please ?
All right , Michael , calm down .
Tomorrow things are gonna change around here ,
so I suggest you live it up tonight .
Judith !
Here .
What ?
Would you do me a favor and please take your brother trick-or-treating ?
Why don 't you have that subhuman sloth over there on the couch do it ?
You know , if I could get that lazy drunk off his fat ass , I would .
Bitch , if you don 't think I ain 't making a mental list of all your fucking bullshit !
Sweetie , look at me .
I know things have been bad ,
but tomorrow we start to make everything better , okay ?
- Yeah . - [ Doorbell rings ]
I like your hair curly . It looks pretty .
Thanks , sweetie . Have fun trick-or-treating , okay ?
Don 't eat too much candy .
Hey , Mrs. Myers .
I want you out by 11 .
- What 'd I do ? - I know what you do .
Whatever .
What about trick-or-treating ?
Are you kidding me ? Go by yourself .
Aren 't you too old for that , anyway ?
Whatever .
Sorry , squirt , but have fun .
[ Kids ] Trick or treat !
# # [ Love Hurts ]
# Love hurts #
# Love scars #
# Love wounds #
# And marks #
# Any heart #
# Not tough #
# Or strong #
# Enough #
# To take a lot of pain #
# Take a lot of pain #
# Love is like a cloud #
# Holds a lot of rain #
# Love hurts #
# Ooh , ooh , love hurts #
[ passionate moaning ]
[ Giggles ]
What if your dad hears us ?
Hold up , man .
That fucking drunk-prick fuck Ronnie ain 't my dad .
Okay , l- - I didn 't know .
My daddy 's in heaven , okay ?
Okay .
I 'm sorry .
Close your eyes .
Keep them closed , all right ?
I got a surprise for you .
Open .
Aaarrrgghhh !
Aaahh ! [ Laughs ]
- Wow . - What ?
Take that stupid thing off .
Oh , come on , babe . I want to do it with the mask on .
[ Music playing on TV ]
[ Snoring ]
[ Candy tinkering on floor ]
[ Candy tinkering ]
[ Snoring ]
[ Laughing from outside ]
[ Muffled gagging ]
[ No audible dialogue ]
Uhh !
Uhh ! Uhh ! Uhh ! Uhh !
[ ( Don 't Fear ) The Reaper playing in headphones ]
[ Giggles ]
Steve , stop it .
Stop .
Once a night is enough .
Stop it .
Michael ?
Michael , what the fuck are you doing in here ?
Answer me . Michael .
Michael !
Answer me !
What the fuck- - Michael !
Answer- -
[ crying ]
[ Knife slicing ]
[ Screaming ]
- [ Knife slicing ] - [ Screaming ]
Happy Halloween , Boo .
[ No audible dialogue ]
Jesus , what the hell happened now ?
Sweetie , what are you doing out here ?
It 's freezing .
Michael , what 's going on ?
Michael , answer me .
Give me the baby .
Michael , what is going on ?
Answer me .
[ Sirens approaching ]
[ Chattering , indistinct ]
[ Screaming ]
... in connection with tonight 's brutal murders .
[ Reporter ] ... the Myers family ,
and was described by police as Manson-like in its viciousness ,
and more horrific than anything Hollywood could imagine .
Judith Myers ' nude body was found lying face-down
in a pool of blood in an upstairs hallway .
Apparently she had been stabbed 17 times .
Her boyfriend Steven Haley 's body was found in the kitchen downstairs ,
the victim of an apparent vicious beating with an aluminum baseball bat .
Along with Myers and Haley ,
a third victim , Ronnie White ,
who was found bound to a chair ,
White 's neck slit wide open with a kitchen knife
and stabbed numerous times in the face and chest .
Of course we 'll have much more on this horrific story as it develops .
But for now , three people brutally murdered ,
and a 10-year-old boy , Michael Myers , being held in custody .
I 'm standing outside Smith 's Grove Sanitarium
where late last night ,
10-year-old Michael Myers was transferred
after being found guilty of first-degree murder .
Myers ' verdict comes after one of the lengthiest
and most expensive trials in the state 's history .
In attendance during this trial , Dr. Samuel Loomis .
Loomis has now been appointed by Judge Masterson
to oversee Myers ' care while incarcerated here at Smith 's Grove .
Hello , hello , hello .
Can you talk in there ?
Hi , I 'm Michael Myers .
Okay , okay . That 's fine .
That 's good . That 's good . Okay , we 're on .
How are you feeling today ?
Good .
Could I ask you something ?
You can ask me whatever you want .
That 's why I 'm here .
If you have anything on your mind , feel free- - anything .
Okay .
Why do you talk so funny ?
Talk so funny ?
Tell me , Michael ,
what do you remember about ...
that night , Halloween ?
What do you mean , like my costume and candy ?
So you remember nothing about the killing ?
You remember nothing about getting a knife ?
- I didn 't do that . - Oh , okay .
But you were covered in blood . Whose blood was it ?
I don 't know .
[ Loomis ] Case : Michael Myers .
To the untrained eye , there 's nothing visually abnormal
with this angelic young boy , but one must remember not to be fooled
by his calm , unassuming facade .
[ Michael ] Can I go home today ?
[ Mrs. Myers ] No , not today .
[ Michael ] Tomorrow ?
I don 't know . I have to talk to the doctor about that .
[ Classical music playing on PA ]
- Hey , Mommy . - Yeah .
Is everyone at home okay ?
Everything 's okay at home .
Okay .
Hey , Mikey .
How you doing ?
Look , you can 't let those walls get you down .
Believe me , I know .
I spent a little time behind walls .
I know they can drive you crazy .
You gotta look beyond the walls .
You know , learn to live inside your head .
Hey , there 's no walls that can stop you there .
All right , I gotta get back to work .
Now you take it easy , Mikey .
Look at my mask .
Oh , wow . Beautiful . Yeah .
Why is it all black ?
'Cause it 's one of my favorite colors .
Well , actually black isn 't a color , is it ?
It 's the absence of color .
In the spectrum of colors ,
you go from black , which is no color ,
all the way through to white ,
which is every color .
So technically- -
not that it really matters- - but black isn 't a color .
Why did you make it ?
I have my secrets .
Wait a minute .
I thought we had no secrets , you and I.
Because no one sees me .
Yes , they do . I see you every day .
Your mom , she comes every week .
Anybody else ?
No .
[ Loomis ] Michael has begun to obsess
on the construction of these primitive masks .
It is the rare occasion that he will allow himself
to be seen without one of these .
Only during the weekly visits from his mother
does he show brief glimpses of the boy he once may have been .
Do you like my mask ?
When did you make this ?
Just yesterday .
I like the mask because it hides my face .
I don 't like you to hide your face .
Take it off .
It hides my ugliness .
Sweetie , don 't say that . Take it off .
You 're not ugly .
Don 't talk like that , okay ?
Okay .
I miss you so much .
I miss you , too .
[ Loomis ] Michael 's so-called normal moments
are becoming fewer and fewer ,
and I 'm particularly worried about this .
I believe that these masks have begun to create a mental sanctuary
in which Michael can hide within himself and from himself .
# Deck the halls with boughs of holly , Fa la la la la , la la la la #
Fuck you ! Fuck you all !
- I hate you ! - Let it out !
Shut the fuck up !
I gotta get out of here .
Just let me out ! I hate this world !
- I don 't want to be here anymore . - I know . It 's okay .
- I just want to go home . - It 's okay . It 's okay .
It 's okay .
Why can 't I just go home ?
Okay .
Okay . Okay . Okay .
I 'm afraid you can 't go home .
Why ?
Because you 've done terrible things .
Come here . Come on .
It 's okay . It 's okay , Michael .
[ Loomis ] Michael 's downward slide
into this hellish abyss continues .
I fear he 's on the verge of completely shutting down .
I managed to persuade the suits to let you come outside
and sit out in the garden .
All right , gardens .
Hardly a charming place , but at least there 's a bit of greenery .
But please , I mean , if you don 't communicate with me ,
how can I help you ?
I 'm here to help you .
I feel an utter failure at the moment ,
that I just can 't get through to you .
And you know , they 're going to see in my reports
that you 're not responding , and- -
you know , they may take me off the case .
I don 't know . I hope not .
I need to get out of here .
Yes , that 's not going to happen for a while , Michael .
Michael , take off the mask .
Honey , you don 't look good . You have to eat . Come on .
- Put my mask back on . - Michael .
Please put my mask back on .
Come on . Let 's try to enjoy the day .
[ Loomis ] The child christened Michael Myers
has become a sort of ghost ,
a mere shape of a human being .
There 's nothing left here now .
[ Classical music playing on PA ]
Well , before I go , I brought you something .
I found it . I thought you might like to hang it up in your room .
I thought you 'd like it .
Well , I guess I 'll see you next week .
I 'll walk you to the car .
Bye , sweetie .
Nurse , sit with Michael . I 'm taking Mrs. Myers to her car .
- Yes , sir . - Thank you .
Cute baby .
Couldn 't be related to you .
You know , he 's been silent now for two weeks almost .
We really may want to consider maybe shock treatments .
[ No audible dialogue ]
What happened ? What happened ?
What happened there ?
Hey !
[ No audible dialogue ]
[ Film projector running ]
[ Gunshot ]
[ Baby crying ]
So you don 't fucking talk a lot , do you , Max ?
Goddamn it , we 're gonna get one thing straight .
I don 't work for you .
You may have worked here for many years
and done all manner of things ,
and I suppose that 's because you 're a hard worker .
Most of you people are .
All your women keep your little bungalows clean ,
sweep off the dirt floors- -
keep the papooses in order and all- -
but I 'm my own boss , all right ?
I retire in about three months ,
and you 're still gonna be here for a long time .
Now open the door .
Don 't take no orders from anybody .
[ Claps hands ] Let 's go , fuck-nut . Time to go .
- Hey ! Don 't touch those . - What ?
He doesn 't like it when you touch the masks .
God damn , I wouldn 't want the bum to freak out .
Sorry about these chains , Mikey .
What do you mean , you 're sorry about these chains ?
You got feelings for this big idiot , is that what it is ?
What 's the dig goin ' on , Ismael ? What the fuck , man ?
You know what ? I 've been taking care of this kid for almost 20 years .
And me and him- -
You know what ? Never mind . Just shut up , man .
Just keep your hands off his things .
Don 't look at me .
I 'll be a shitstorm in your worst nightmare , motherfucker .
I 'll come in here and fuck this place up one night , you watch .
[ Loomis ] I really don 't know what else to say , Michael .
You haven 't said a word for 15 years .
Christ , that 's a lifetime .
That 's nearly twice as long as my first marriage .
Wow .
It 's strange , Michael .
In a weird way , you 've become like
like my best friend .
It just shows you how fucked up my life is .
I 've done all I possibly can for you .
So I 'm sorry to tell you
that this is going to be my last day .
Michael ...
I have to move on .
I 'm sorry .
Take care , Michael .
Take care .
These eyes will deceive you .
They will destroy you .
They will take from you your innocence ...
your pride ...
and eventually your soul .
These eyes do not see what you and I see .
Behind these eyes one finds only blackness ,
the absence of light .
These are the eyes ...
of a psychopath .
Michael was created
by a perfect alignment
of interior and exterior factors
gone violently wrong- -
a perfect storm , if you will .
Thus creating a psychopath
that knows no boundaries ...
and has no boundaries .
[ Buzzers sounding ]
[ Door slamming ]
Kendall , I really don 't appreciate
being called out of my favorite watering hole
to come down on the fuckin ' graveyard shift .
If you do me dirt on this one , I 'll fuckin ' hold it against you .
Hey , you know what ? I 'll fuck her . You don 't want to fuck her ?
I 'll fuck her . Right here .
Mikey , Mikey , Mikey .
Here we go . I want you to meet Cousin Noel .
- Hi , there , sweetie . Hi . - Huh ?
Oh , we 're just here to look in on you .
We know it 's your first night and all .
We just want to see how you are . Oh !
- Aren 't you a pretty little thing ? - Not bad , huh ?
We 're just makin ' sure everything 's okay .
Oh , now , we 're okay . Hey . Ooh , look at those little titties .
You 're right ! Oh , look at there .
- What else is under there ? - [ Screaming ]
No , no , no , no , no . Oh , yeah ! Whoo !
We got ourselves a fighter !
A fresh one ! You done good , cousin .
Hah-hah !
- I got an idea . - Okay .
I got me a fuckin ' bona fide , sure as shit idea !
- Keep her fuckin ' quiet . - God , shut up .
[ Door opens , slams shut ]
[ Kendall ] Oh , Mikey , Mikey , Mikey , Mikey , Mikey .
Hello , Mike !
Hey , Mikey . We brought you a little company .
Yeah , we got you some new , fresh meat , baby .
Fuckin ' bitch . You want some of that ?
- Come on , baby ! - [ Whimpers ]
- Show us you 're a man , huh ? - [ Screams ]
You want some fuckin ' pussy ?
[ Sniffs ] Yeah .
You want some fuckin ' pussy , huh ?
Yeah . Mm , that 's good . How ' bout some of that , killer ?
He ain 't gonna do it . Let me lick- -
Let me just- -
- You wanna fuckin ' fight , huh ? - [ Screams ]
- Come on , bitch . - Fuck the shit outta her .
- Come on ! Get on her ! - Yeah , baby !
You fucking tard-ass faggot , come on !
Yeah !
You a faggot , boy ?
[ All screaming ]
You a faggot , huh ?
What the fuck ?
Hey , you son of a bitch !
Son of a bitch ! Let him go .
Kendall !
What the fuck , Mikey ? It 's Kendall .
It 's Kendall , Mikey .
[ Telephone rings ]
[ Ring ]
Gloria ?
[ Breathing erratically ]
[ Ring ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Speaking in Spanish ]
En el nombre del Padre , y del Hijo , y del Espiritu Santo ...
Mikey , what are you doing out of your room ?
Okay ...
Now , don 't do nothing
we 're both gonna regret later , okay , Mikey ?
I 'm gonna have to get you back into your room , okay now ?
Let me get these .
I 'm just gonna ...
get these handcuffs and ...
I 'm gonna try to put these handcuffs on you right now , Mikey .
And then we 'll get you back into your own bed , okay ?
Mikey !
I was good to you , Mikey .
[ Coughing ]
- [ Crash ] - [ Telephone rings ]
[ Ring ]
Hello .
- Sam . - Who is this ?
Sam , it 's Koplenson .
Who ?
Dr. Koplenson from Smith 's Grove .
He 's out .
Michael 's out .
Shit . What ?
He broke out a few hours ago .
Sam , it 's a- - it 's a fucking massacre .
I 'm coming right away . All right .
Oh , shit .
# # [ " Tom Sawyer " ]
# A modern-day warrior Mean , mean stride #
# Today 's Tom Sawyer Mean , mean pride #
[ horn honks ]
Oh , fuck !
Gotta leave the truck .
All right , boys .
Grizzley 's back in town . Who 's got the Cracker Jacks ?
Grizzley 's back !
All right !
Look it here .
That 's a new paint job .
Don 't mess it up . Don 't scratch it .
Yeah .
Oh , man .
Oh , my goodness .
Ooh !
# The world is , the world is love and ... #
Naughty girl .
Naughty , naughty girl .
Hey , buddy , just to give you a heads up ,
I got a taco deluxe supreme talking back at me ,
so I 'm going to be a while .
So do you mind waiting somewhere else and let me pass this beast in peace ?
Look , brother ...
if you 're looking for some kind of action ,
you better take it on the arches before I 'm done dropping this load .
Or you 're going to be one sorry A-hole .
I see .
What we got here is ...
a failure to communicate .
You just hold on , Daisy .
I 've got something for you .
Let me introduce myself .
I 'm Joe Grizzley , bitch .
And I 'm going to cut that mask right off your face , you- -
Get- - Get back !
I ain 't scared !
Come on , what- -
# Mr. Sandman ... #
Mason , Laurie !
- Morning . - [ Sighs ]
Where are my goddamn glasses ?
- Jesus , Cynth , I 'm gonna be late . - On your head .
- Oh , sh- - I 'm gonna lose my mind . - Move .
Excuse me .
- You gotta be kidding me . - Now what ?
It says here Nickel 's Hardware is going out of business .
42 years and that 's it , over and done .
Yeah , well , good . They 're a rip-off .
And Mr. Nickels is a horny old pervert .
Okay , don 't even want to know .
Guess what , Mom .
Mr. Nickels likes to touch me the wrong way .
Ooh , whoo , Mommy !
Okay , that is so not funny .
Want a screwdriver , Mommy ? You want a hammer ?
Look at this , Mom . Oh !
- Laurie , stop ! - I 'm sorry . Okay .
- Are you eating ? - No , I 'll get something at school .
- Oh , my God . - [ Dad ] Oh , sure .
Just let the faceless marauding corporate monsters of America
destroy everything beautiful about this town .
Corporate monsters or not , Epic Mart 's a lot cheaper .
Oh , man , I gotta get out of here .
- Thanks again for dropping that thing off . - No sweat , Dad .
Just shove the envelope inside the mail slot , okay ?
Yeah , Dad , I know .
They 're coming by to look at it later , honey .
- So , it 's very important that- - - Dad , okay .
I understand . Muy importante .
- Love you . - Love you , too .
Have a good day .
Mason , you forgot your briefcase , honey .
- Ah , shit . - Ah , shit .
I feel like " What round is it ? "
Yeah .
Oh , uh , you think you could ... glue Mr. Bones ' arms on or something ?
- Have a good day , baby . - Yeah . Top on my priority list .
Hey , Laurie !
- Wait up ! - Oh , God .
- Leave me alone , Tommy . - Wait .
Definition : Stop walking .
- Can I ask you something serious ? - Sure , why not ?
Did you ever hear about the Mexican Wolf Man ?
- No . - Yeah , well , he 's real .
- I saw him on TV last night ... - Yeah .
And his name 's Danny , and his face is completely covered with hair .
And he likes soccer . I swear it ! They showed- -
- Okay . - He 's a wolf !
Tommy , I have no idea what you 're talking about .
Lay off the candy corn , kid .
Stop acting like I 'm crazy . It 's true !
Tommy , I 'm your babysitter . You 're crazy .
- I know this . You 're crazy . - Ooohhh !
[ Laurie ] All right , gotta make a stop here .
[ Tommy ] Whoa ! What are you , insane ?
Oh , my gosh , Tommy , I 'm not even listening to you .
You 'd better listen to me .
He 's right there .
What are you , crazy ? You can 't go in there .
Oh , yes , I can .
Hold my books , please ?
That 's the devil 's house . The Boogey Man lives in there .
Yeah . Oh , no , Tommy .
Don 't even joke about it . I 'm serious .
Oh , you 're scaring me .
The Boogey Man will get me or Danny the Wolf Man .
Oh , no , Tommy .
Oh , no !
Oh , no , it 's pulling me- -
Oh , no , Tommy , it 's pulling me in !
Ha ha ha .
It was just a joke . Chill .
I wish it wasn 't .
Come on , hurry up .
Chill , spazz-monkey .
Thanks .
That 's no place to screw around , Laurie .
- It 's not a big deal . - Not a big deal ?
Do you know whose house that is ?
Come on .
- It 's going to be fine . - Yeah .
What if something happens ?
- Laurie , what is going to happen ? - I don 't know .
It 's going to be fine .
What is going to be fine ?
Annie wants me to pretend to baby-sit Lindsey Wallace ,
then sneak out and dump her with me so she can go and see Paul .
Sounds like one of my crafty ideas .
- Yeah . - I like it .
Anyway , I thought Paul was , like , grounded for trashing his dad 's motorcycle .
Oh , yeah . No , he was , but he got out of it .
- You know . - Yeah .
Please ?
What if they come home early ?
Dude , they are not going to come home early .
Okay ? Mrs. Wallace is a lush .
They 're going to be out all night getting hammered .
Yeah . Annie , I really hate lying . You know that .
God , what are you , Mother Teresa ?
- No . - Yes , she is .
Look at her . She 's like a little angel .
- She 's Mother-fucking Teresa . - Stop . I am not !
Please ?
- All right , I 'll do it . - Yes !
You owe me big time .
- I love you . - I love you .
Did you know that ethyl alcohol boils at 78.5 degrees Celsius ?
- I didn 't know that . - Yeah .
That 's pretty cool , right ?
Call me back .
This is all your fault .
I mean , you 're responsible .
I cannot be responsible for everything that goes on in here .
- What about you ? - No , no , no , no .
You 're not pinning this on me .
- He was your patient , Doctor . - Was my patient .
Look , all you guys had to do was to play zoo-keeper .
Just keep the monkeyhouse locked until the monkey died of old age .
How difficult is that ?
Christ , you can barely tell he 's breathing half the time .
He 's been like a comatose kitty for 15 years .
If our security wasn 't sufficient , Sammy ,
you should have warned us .
I see . So you 're just going to wash your hands of the whole thing .
You know , you two make me sick .
" He is mad that trusts in the tameness of a wolf . "
We 've given the authorities his complete profile .
Two road blocks and an all-points bulletin wouldn 't stop a 5-year-old .
Well , what do you want us to do ?
Yes . I mean , what do you want us to do ?
I want you to get on the phone ,
and I want you to tell them who broke out of here last night .
And I want you to tell them exactly where he 's going .
Christ , we don 't know where he 's going .
It must be great living in denial .
I must try it sometime .
Look , you and that army of shirt-tuckers up there ,
you know damn well where he 's going .
And where is that ?
Haddonfield !
Haddonfield 's a hundred miles away from here .
[ School bell rings ]
This is so fucked .
What , me suspended from the squad ?
I don 't mean to sound conceited ,
but I 'm , like , the fucking hottest cheerleader they 've got .
Yeah , Lynda , that doesn 't sound conceited .
What , so now nobody can take a joke anymore ?
- What did you say ? - Check it .
So Lady Fuck-face gives us three new cheers to learn ,
so I 'm like , " Hey , why don 't we just rock it commando , flash some snatch ?
And maybe nobody will notice we 're doing the same old tired cheers . "
- Oh , you didn 't . - Oh , yeah , I did .
- Yeah , you did . - Yeah .
You know what that dried-up fucking bitch did ?
- What ? - Calls my dad and tells him what I said .
- Yeah . - Oh , my gosh .
That C-U-N-T , yeah , needs to get laid .
What did your dad say ?
Oh , who cares ?
I 'll just give him the little sweetie-pants princess suck-up routine .
Daddy 's little pookie would never say something like that .
Gosh , ever since your parents split up ,
you have your dad wrapped around your little finger .
Totally wrapped .
- Hey , bitches ! - Hey , Annie .
- Thanks for waiting for me . - Whatever . Hurry your ass up .
God .
Hey , I heard about your little cheerleading incident .
Yeah , I 'm totally famous .
You 're totally a slut .
Yeah . [ Laughs ]
Anyway , today in class , in French class ,
Mr. Leclerc was totally flirting with me .
- God , here we go ! - We were conjugating the verb " to want . "
- Because he so wants you ! - Je veuxl Je veuxl
- Oh , my gosh . - Bare Leclerc .
Bare Leclerc wants me .
I think that guy 's watching us .
- What guy ? - That guy over there .
Yeah ?
- Oh , please . - I saw him outside school earlier .
Probably just some pervert cruising school poontang .
Yeah , wait . Watch this .
Hey , freak !
Hey , freak , you want some of the young stuff ?
You like that ? Well , come and get it .
- Hey ! - Lynda , stop .
Hey , asshole . My daddy 's the sheriff .
Huh ? Why don 't you go crawl back under your fucking rock ?
- Yeah , whatever . - See , I told you .
He 's just some stupid fucking pervert .
- Total pervert . - Gosh , you guys are crazy .
That guy could have been dangerous .
- Oh , God . - Whatever .
- What is he going to do ? - I don 't know .
Oh , my God . You should date him !
- You should ! - You guys !
Come on , let 's go get something- -
[ horn honks ]
- Oh , no , 5-0 . - Hey .
Hi , Dad .
Hey , Mr. Brackett .
- Nice furry hat , Mr. Brackett . - Thank you .
What 's up , Dad ?
I 'm on my way home . Anybody want a ride ?
Yeah . Hell , yeah , I 'll take a ride .
- No . - You guys ?
Bacon-mobiles make me nauseous .
- Nice . - Bye , Annie .
- See you later . - Bye , guys .
Hey , kiddo .
- Kind of a drag having a pig as a dad . - Nah , I like him .
Yeah ? Do you think he was flirting with me ?
- You are so demented . - Totally .
- Yeah . See ya . - Bye .
- I hate you ! - [ Laughs ]
Aw , how cute .
Would you please help me with this stupid thing ?
Okay , okay , okay .
Jeez . Mom , why do you deal with this every year ?
Because for some unbelievable reason ,
your father likes it .
- The feet look like the hands- - - It 's not working .
And the hands like the feet , and I can 't get the thing in the hole , and- -
- Oh , I can 't get it ! - Calm down , I 'm helping- -
Oh , I got it .
- You got it ? - Will you try and get those right ?
Okay , I 'll try .
Oh , jeez .
I 've been out here for two hours doing this .
There .
- Hey , do you want me to get- - - Just hang himself . No !
I 'm still upset about the whole bagel thing this morning ,
if you want to know the truth .
Mom , that was a joke .
- Oh , yeah . Well , let me tell you . - It was a joke .
There are some things moms don 't need to hear .
- Yeah , I 'm 17 . - I know you 're 17 .
You 're the best , Mom . [ Chuckles ]
[ Man ] Yeah , it 's right over here .
[ Loomis on phone ] Yeah . Hello ?
Yes , uh , Sheriff Brackett , please .
Dr. Samuel Loomis . Yeah . Hello ? He- -
Oh , sh- - ugh ! Can I borrow your cell phone ?
This thing 's about as useful as a row of Christmas puddings .
[ Chuckles ] Oh , no . I don 't have one .
Causes brain cancer .
Oh , yeah . Right .
You know , I remember this mess just like it happened yesterday ?
It was tragic .
The poor woman , I guess she couldn 't stand the stress
of being labeled " Satan 's mother . "
I think she blew her fucking head off .
I 'm still amazed .
A young boy like that butchering all those people .
And the doctor involved- - I think he wrote a book or something .
Fucking blood money .
Yeah , I read that book . It was a masterpiece .
- Now , are we close ? - Yes , it 's just here . I gu- -
- Goddamn son of a bitch ! - What ?
Those fucking kids ! Jesus Christ !
Don 't they think I have anything better to do with my time than clean up this shit ?
Fucking little idiots ! God damn it !
Where the hell are you going ?
Who would do sick shit like this ?
I think I know whose grave that is .
[ Turns engine off ]
Dude , it fucking totally sucks that they 're selling this place .
It 's reduced . Maybe I can buy it .
Yeah , with like , your $ 10 you have in your piggy bank ?
It 's a shithole anyway .
I 'm going to miss it .
Don 't worry , dude .
We 'll find another house to party in .
Besides , I 'm gonna get the van all jacked up .
You 're gonna want to spend more time in there anyway .
[ Passionate moaning ]
Wait , wait !
Wait , just like that .
Oh , God .
Oh , wait . Wait .
Right there , right there .
- Hold on ! - Wait , my calf is cramping , man .
Why 'd you stop ? Oh , God- -
Oh , fuck .
A fucking little warning would be nice .
- Fuck . - I 'm sorry .
Jesus .
- Get me another beer . - You get it .
I 'm the one that just did all the heavy lifting .
All right , I 'll go .
So , seriously , on a scale from 1 to 10 , should I have a 5 ?
How about ... zero ?
- More like- - - Zero .
More like zero plus 11 .
[ Radio playing ]
[ Changing radio dials ]
[ " ( Don 't Fear ) The Reaper " playing on radio ]
[ Ringing ]
- Hello ? - Yo , Mama .
What up , dude ?
- Nothing much . - Oh , what 's wrong ?
I was just thinking about what Annie said earlier today ,
concerning my so-called " cheerleading incident . "
I don 't know . It 's kind of bumming me out .
Fuck , dude , who put all the empties back in here ?
You don 't think that , do you ?
Lynda , I don 't think you 're a slut .
Come on , that 's ridiculous .
I don 't give a shit what Annie thinks anyway .
But I care what you think .
Aww !
Fuck !
What- - What the f- -
Jesus , Bob , could you move your pokey ass a little slower ?
Well , could you ?
Well , that 's cute .
See anything you like ?
Okay , enough .
Joke 's over .
Beer , please .
Hey , Casper the Friendly Asshole Ghost , hand me my beer .
Well , fucking hand it over , dip-shit .
Why do you have to become such a fucking jerk every time we do it ?
You think you 'd be grateful that I let you touch me with that thing .
And anyway , you 're not a zero .
You 're a fucking minus 5 or something .
Whatever .
What 'd you do to this beer ?
What about this big one here ? That looks perfect .
- You mean , like , this one here ? - Yeah , that one .
- Yes , yes , that 's lovely . - .22 Smith Wesson .
- That 's good . - Yeah .
That 's okay if you want to just piss it off .
If you want to blow its fucking head off ...
this is what you want .
.357 Magnum .
Wolff mainspring , polygonal rifling .
Beautiful , beautiful . Poly what ?
- Muzzle velocity of 1,450 feet per second . - Great , just wrap it up .
- That 's fine . - Okay , okay .
- Take it easy . - Thank you . Yes .
I 'm in a bit of a hurry .
If you could just wrap it up , that 'd be great .
- Thank you . - What are we hunting ?
- Girls , you look so beautiful . - Little princesses .
- Trick or treat . - Here you go .
- Thank you . - Here 's some candy .
- Oh , Happy Halloween . - You , too .
- Bye , you guys . - Thank you . Bye .
So cute .
I cannot believe you 're graduating this year .
I remember when you used to run around looking like that .
Mom , I was never a princess .
Last thing I was at their age was dead Little Red Riding Hood .
You were this beautiful ballerina- -
No , you bought me the blood and you gave me the cuts .
" My costume 's too tight . "
- You don 't remember that ? - I never wore a tutu .
You getting many kids ?
Only two so far .
Listen ...
be careful tonight .
I know .
A lot of nut cases come out on Halloween .
It 's , uh- - What was it you told me to say ?
- Amateur night . - Yeah , that 's right . Amateur night .
Dad , I 'm just going to be babysitting .
- What 's the worst thing I could do ? - All right , okay .
- I 'm just saying . - Nice .
- All right . - Sorry .
- Aah ! - Mom , st- -
Hi , Mr. And Mrs. Strode !
- Hey , Annie . - Hey .
How 's your dad ?
Oh , you know , same as always .
- You know what that means ? - Mm-hmm .
Yeah . Love you guys !
- Love you , too ! - Bye-bye !
Gonna give me some lovin ' ?
I 'll give you some lovin ' later , but first you 're going to talk about the vacation .
I 'm going to go build a fire .
Vacation .
I hate vacation . Let 's stay home .
Aaahhh !
No ! No !
You leave my baby alone , you- -
[ crack ]
Okay , Tommy , here 's your jelly sandwich ,
hold the peanut butter .
Good .
You know , if you listened to me the first time ,
you wouldn 't had to have made it twice .
- Laurie ? - What ?
Is the Boogey Man real ?
Why are you so obsessed with the Boogey Man , Tommy ?
- Well , I hear things at school . - Like what ?
Well , I heard that on Halloween night ,
the Boogey Man sneaks out and attacks kids who don 't believe .
You know what , Tommy ?
It is true .
He likes to eat little boys like you .
Oh , my God ! The Boogey Man 's here !
We 're going to die !
[ Telephone rings ]
Hold that thought .
That 's not appropriate babysitter behavior , Laurie .
Hello ?
[ Laurie ] Shut up .
- My parents will hear about this one . - Yo , it 's me . Hey .
So the Wallaces are finally out of my face .
I just talked to Paul . He 's on his way over .
So I 'm finishing making the Queen of Sheba her popcorn , and then I will be over .
I have some fun and exciting news for you , so I 'll see you in a few minutes .
Okay , bye .
- Guess what , Tommy . - What ?
Lindsey Wallace is coming over .
What ? She can 't come over here !
- What if the guys see her ? - So ?
One , she 's a girl .
Two , she 's not a boy .
And three , she smells like you .
This is going to be a long night .
For the both of us .
- Don 't start with me . - Uh , uh .
What 's the matter with you ?
Lindsey ... get your coat on .
We 're going to go over and see Tommy Doyal .
Okay .
- What are you doing ? - Nothing .
Yeah , exactly . I said get your coat on .
We 're going over to your late-night lover Tommy Doyal 's house .
No , you didn 't .
Yes , I did .
Don , I 'm sorry if I don 't sound too concerned ,
but a dead coyote and a missing headstone doesn 't prove anything .
Well , I think you 're wrong , Sheriff .
I think it does prove that he 's here in Haddonfield .
It was a Halloween prank .
Kids pull shit like that all the time .
The stone will be returned tomorrow .
And besides , it weighs over half a ton .
That 's my point exactly .
So you 're saying that one man picked it up and walked away with it ?
Yes .
Doc , I may have been born , but I wasn 't born yesterday .
I 'm sorry , Sheriff , but please listen to me .
This may be a matter of life and death .
All right , I 'll tell you what I 'll do .
You come by my office tomorrow- -
Tomorrow is too late .
Evil is here .
It 's walking amongst us .
Doc , it sounds to me like you 're talking about the Antichrist .
Well , perhaps I am .
Smell my feet
Give me something good to eat
If you don 't , I don 't care
I 'll pull down Annie 's underwear
I can 't believe you 're making me haul this thing all the way over there .
I can 't believe you think I 'm not going to tell .
Gonna share some popcorn with your little boyfriend ?
No , I 'm not .
You know you are .
You know you 're going to share something with Paul .
You know how annoying you are ?
How ?
Trick or treat , smell my feet .
Give me something good to eat
- If you don 't , I don 't care- - - I swear to God , Lindsey .
If you don 't stop singing that song ,
we 're going to have a pumpkin-smashing party
right here in the middle of the street .
[ Doorbell rings ]
Tommy , where 's your girlfriend Laurie ?
Laurie 's not my girlfriend . I hate girls .
Why doesn 't anyone understand this ?
Good . So does Lindsey .
Go worship your god .
- Hey . - Brought you a present .
Thanks .
You , my dear , will be happy to know
that I talked to Paul about his buddy Ben Tramer .
Oh , I thought you said Ben Tramer was retarded .
Yeah , but he 's not Shortbus retarded or anything .
What ? He 's okay .
- I mean , you need a boyfriend ! - Annie , I don 't need a boyfriend .
- No , that 's not what I meant . - I 'm fine .
- You need- - - Okay , Annie- -
Oh ! Oh ! Yes !
Yes , Annie !
Okay , ok- -
All right , you 're right .
I need a boyfriend .
So , what did he say ?
He said , and I quote ,
" Dude , she 's fucking hot . "
- Really ? - Uh-huh .
[ Honks horn ]
Oh , fuck , that 's Paul . I gotta go .
- Have fun . - Thanks , I will .
- Bye , sexy . - Bye .
Hi , baby .
- What 's up ? - How are you ?
I 'm good . How are you ?
Good .
You have to stop thinking that we 're dealing with a normal man here .
We 're dealing with a soulless killing machine ,
driven by pure animal instinct .
Dr. Loomis , I 'm going to have to level with you .
I read your book .
I know exactly who you are , and frankly , I don 't like you .
And I 'll tell you something else .
I think you have created quite the masterpiece of a monster
off the blood of this town , because monsters sell books .
Please , just look at this photograph on the cover of the book .
All right .
I first met Michael 17 years ago .
When I first met him , he was a sweet , charming little boy .
But he had nothing inside .
There was something missing , a void .
There was no conscience , no reason ,
even a rudimentary sense of life or death , right or wrong .
Yeah . He 's come back for her .
And who is her ?
He 's come back for his baby sister .
I know it in my bones , Sheriff .
To do what ?
I don 't know , Sheriff , but ...
it 's not good .
If I break a promise I made a long time ago ,
then you must promise that you will play it
razor , and I mean razor , straight with me .
[ Telephone rings ]
[ Mr. Strode , on machine ] Hello . You have reached the Strode residence .
[ Mrs. Strode ] We can 't come to the phone right now .
[ Mr. Strode ] So please leave a message and have a ...
[ both ] Happy Halloweenl
[ beep ]
Yeah , this is Sheriff Brackett . Hello ?
If you can hear me , pick up .
Please , if you can hear me , I need to talk to you immediately .
[ Hangs up phone ]
Let 's go .
- Laurie ? - What , Tommy ?
I would like to return to the subject we started earlier this evening .
What ? Your hatred of peanut butter ?
No , the Boogey Man .
I need some closure on this topic .
I 've heard all about this .
What do you want to know , Tommy ?
Why would he only attack kids who don 't believe ?
I mean , it doesn 't make sense .
Is it because if you believe , then you 're protected by his powers ?
Okay , Tommy , enough about the Boogey Man .
It 's nonsense .
I 'm with Tommy on this one .
Yeah . Why do you keep avoiding the subject , Laurie ?
Is- - Is she scared ?
- Maybe she is . - Ooh , yeah .
- Maybe you 're scared ! - Are you scared ?
Okay , stop ! Stop !
Leave me alone for five seconds , please .
- Five , four , three ... - You guys ...
- Okay , please don 't . - Two , one .
No ! No !
I 'm going to tell your parents !
Hey , don 't pull it like that . You 're going to stretch it all out .
- Come on , munchie . - Stop . This is expensive , idiot .
- You want to fuck me ? - Yeah .
- Yeah ? - You 're so fucking hot , babe .
You want to fuck me ? I want to hear you say it .
- I 'm gonna fuck you . - Yeah ?
Say it again .
It 's so fucking warm .
Oh , my- -
What 's the matter ?
[ Screaming ]
[ Dogs barking ]
[ Moaning ]
[ Crying ]
Lindsey , it 's time for you to go home .
But the movie 's not over .
You can finish watching the movie at your house .
- How about during the commercial break ? - Negative .
Go get your jacket !
You heard her , girl . Keep on marching .
Ugh ! I am Queen Sheba , okay ?
- Bow down and worship me . - Go get your jacket .
Are you sure you 're okay while I take Lindsey home ?
- I 'm fine . - Are you sure , little Tommy ?
- You 'll be by yourself ! - I 'm fine , now stop asking !
- Are you sure ? - Yes !
- He 's scared . - No , I 'm not .
- Yes , you are . - Shut up .
Okay , you guys . Stop .
Behave , Tommy-Wommy . [ Giggling ]
[ Siren wailing ]
About 17 years ago , I respond to a 911
which turned out to be the Myers woman 's suicide .
And I see this beautiful , innocent baby sitting in this bloody mess ,
and I can 't imagine this child growing up with a stigma around her neck ,
so I omit her from the report , I drive her to another town ,
and drop her off at the nearest emergency room .
And I think that this is going to be the end of it .
About three months later , I find out from a friend of mine ,
Mason Strode , that he 's adopted the baby .
Oh , my God .
- Cold ? - Yeah .
Okay , come here .
- Did you have fun ? - Yeah .
You sure ?
Yeah .
Annie ? We 're coming in .
You better be decent .
- Where are the lights ? - Here .
[ Screams ]
Annie !
Oh , my God !
Lindsey , run home !
Go call the police ! Go !
Help ! Help ! Help !
Oh , my God , honey ! Are you okay ?
Oh , baby , what happened ?
- He 's in- - - I 'm going to call the police .
Okay ? I promise .
Shit !
- 911 . - I need an ambulance , please !
My friend 's bleeding to death .
[ Crying ]
Laurie !
My name is Laurie Strode , and I 'm at 1987 Winchester Drive .
We have a 911 call , 1987 Winchester Drive .
This is Brackett .
What 's the nature of the emergency and who called it in ?
Two-stabbing-victim call placed by a Laurie Strode .
He 's found her ! He 's found her , for God 's sake !
- How long 's it going to take to get there ? - It 's about ten minutes .
Laurie !
Please , you 've got to help her .
Baby ! Baby , hold on , okay ? Annie , they 're com- -
Help !
Help ! Please !
Help , please ! Someone !
Tommy !
Tommy , open the door !
Open the door ! Tommy , open the door !
Tommy ! Open the door !
Open the door ! Tommy ! Open the door !
What 's going on ?
What 's happening ?
Where 's Lindsey , Tommy ?
- Where 's Lindsey ? - She 's right there !
- She 's upstairs ! - I 'm right here .
Go upstairs !
Tommy , go upstairs !
Guys , get in the bathroom !
- He 's coming ! - Stop ! Shh !
Tommy , be quiet , please ?
[ Chatter on TV , indistinct ]
I got this . You check upstairs .
Right .
This is the police . Are you all right ?
He 's out there ! Please help us !
The door 's locked .
Are you able to unlock the door ?
Are you able to open the door ?
Yeah .
Laurie , no .
Is he gone ?
No , there 's no one out here .
Please , just unlock the door .
Yeah , hold on .
- No ! - Open the door .
Oh , God !
Freeze !
Aah !
[ Screaming ]
[ Sirens approaching ]
Stay behind me .
Annie ?
Sweetie ?
Annie .
Annie . Oh , sweetie .
Stay with me . Stay with me .
They 'll be here soon . Come on , darling .
Jesus .
Over here !
Inside here !
- Boogey Man ! - Help !
Guys , over here !
- The Boogey Man ! - What is it ?
Help ! The Boogey Man !
- What ? What ? - He 's over there !
He took Laurie . He took Laurie away .
Okay , guys .
Go over and stand by that ambulance and just wait there .
Don 't move !
Lynda ?
Lynda , wake up !
Lynda , wake up , please !
Lynda , please wake up !
Lynda , please ! Please , please , please wake up !
He 's going to come soon .
Lynda , wake up , please !
Who are you ?
What do you want ?
No , no , please .
Please don 't hurt us , please !
No , please don 't hurt me , please !
I don 't understand .
Please , just let- - Please leave me alone !
I don 't know them ! Please !
I want to help you .
I just don 't understand .
I just don 't know how .
I want to help you .
I don 't- -
You motherfucker !
[ Screaming ]
Someone help me !
Shit . Let me out !
Fuck !
Let me out !
Somebody , please help me !
Please ! Somebody , please !
Get off ! Help me !
Please , please .
Please .
Help ! Somebody , please !
No , please , please .
Help ! Help !
Somebody , please !
Please . Please .
No . No . No .
Shit .
Please ! Somebody !
Michael ! Stop !
Michael , it 's me ... Samuel .
Michael , please stop !
Help ! Please !
Please ! Stop !
Stop ! Michael !
Shit .
Help !
Stop !
Please .
Help me , please .
It 's all right . It 's all right .
You 're safe now . It 's okay .
Ow , my leg .
It 's okay .
It 's all right .
Was that the Boogey Man ?
As a matter of fact , I do believe it was .
Jesus Christ ! What the hell ?
Michael , don 't !
Michael , stop !
For God 's sake , listen to me !
Look ... it 's not her fault .
Michael , it 's my fault .
I failed you .
Please , let her go . Please .
Open !
[ Thump ]
[ Pounding continues ]
[ Screams ]
[ Click ]
[ Spits ]
[ Screams ]
[ Sirens approaching ]
[ Screaming continues ]
# Mr. Sandman #
# Bring me a dream #
# Make him the cutest that I 've ever seen #
# Give him two lips like roses and clover #
# Then tell him that his lonesome nights are over #
# Sandman #
# I 'm so alone #
# Don 't have nobody to call my own #
# Please turn on your magic beam #
# Mr. Sandman , bring me a dream #
# Mr. Sandman #
# Bring me a dream #
# Make him the cutest that I 've ever seen #
# Give him the word that I 'm not a rover #
# And tell him that his lonesome nights are over #
# Sandman , I 'm so alone #
# Don 't have nobody to call my own #
# Please turn on your magic beam #
# Mr. Sandman , bring me a dream #
# Mr. Sandman #
# Bring us a dream #
# Give him a pair of eyes with a " come-hither " gleam #
# Give him a lonely heart #
# Like Pagliacci #
# And lots of wavy hair like Liberace #
# Mr. Sandman #
# Someone to hold #
# Would be so peachy before we 're too old #
# So please turn on your magic beam #
# Mr. Sandman , bring us #
# Please , please bring us #
# Mr. Sandman #
# Bring us a dream #